It's speeding past the exit light
I see the skyline start to fade A memory of a
choice I made I'm looking in the rearview mirror
The past is getting clearer Was it all just a
mistake? A heart that's learning how to break
It's all in our rearview mirror
This neon glow feels cold and thin
I don't know where I'm supposed to begin
I'm just a passenger in this ride With all the
starbusts left inside I'm looking in the
rearview mirror
The past is getting nearer Was it all just a
mistake? A heart that's learning how to fade
It's all remembering you now
I'm driving fast but I'm not free
Just running from the girl I used to be
I'm looking in the rearview mirror
The past is getting clearer Was it all just a
mistake? A heart that's learning how to break
It's all in the rearview mirror